# Lisa Cadieux

## Trilingual hotel receptionist



#### Personal Info

#### Phone

+33 6 38 42 33 14

#### E-mail

lisacadieux@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/lisacadieux11

## Languages

French

Native

English

Fluent, TOEIC 910

German



Hotel receptionist with a Bachelor's degree from Vatel Hotel Management School, and one year of experience split in two hotels (luxurious and family hotels). Fluent in English, French and German. Great presentation, adaptation and courtesy helped hotels reach their highest satisfaction rate and largest number of five-star reviews during my two work placements. Eager to bring

## Experience

### 2018-01 - Hotel Receptionist

2018-06 Shangri-La Hotel, Paris

- Operated guests' check ins and outs as smoothly and quickly as possible (also sped up the secure deposit box process).
- · Took all initiatives to solve guests' requests and complaints in a timely manner.

my organisational skills to Aloft London Excel.

- Ensured that guests' feedback always reached the reception's supervisor, and was acted on.
- Created a follow-up email flow that doubled the amount of positive reviews received on Google and TripAdvisor, in three languages.

#### 2017-02 - Front Office Assistant

2017-07

Kyriad Hotel Disneyland Paris

- · Assisted the Front Office Manager with two daily reports regarding all services.
- Provided friendly customer service at all time, increasing satisfaction scores by 50%.
- Made a feedback form allowing guests to report any issue or suggest improvements.
- · Liaised with all other departments to help with staff shortage or urgent matters.

#### Education

2015 - MA (Hons), International Hotel Management

2018 Vatel Hotel & Tourism Business School, Lyon

2012 - Baccalauréat (eq. A-levels: Economy, Sociology & Foreign

<sup>5</sup> languages)

Lycée du Parc, Lyon

## Skills

- Adaptability: Conformed with hotels' main market and public smoothly, able to switch languages naturally.
- Communication skills: Maintained a high satisfaction by always being courteous, available and clear with both guests and team collaboration.
- Time management: Handled urgent matters or high guest traffic with ease in a timely manner and with great organisation.
- MS Office Suite: Full IT proficiency with MS Word and Excel enabled data entry and feedback follow-up.

## Volunteering

Volunteer for Restos du Coeur charity during Christmas holidays (since 2015)